In Bitlife, you can do delinquent actions. When you try to do delinquent actions, the character's journal will say 'I felt immature inclinations'.
Sometimes, a relative with high craziness or a sibling will insist you to engage you as a mischief, with a risk of being reprimanded by a parent, being arrested or addicted to alcohol. When you refused to be a mischief, your relationship bar will lower.
The next delinquent actions includes:

Contents

1 Disorderly Conduct
2 Criminal Mischief
3 Reckless Endangerment
4 Assault and Larceny
5 Piracy and Illegal Gambling
6 Twerking
7 All Delinquent Actions
8 Consequences



Disorderly Conduct[]
These are things like pitch invading at games, pulling fire alarms in apartment complexes and releasing pigs into high schools. Such actions may get you 1 year in jail.

Criminal Mischief[]
These are things like tagging places, writing things like ôSorry about your wall!ö or ôTag! You're it!ö Others include blowing up mailboxes and vandalizing stop signs.

Reckless Endangerment[]
These include throwing beer bottles onto oncoming traffic, setting dog feces on fire, or dancing in the middle of a crosswalk. 

Assault and Larceny[]
These involve slapping people down the street or stealing street signs/bikes.

Piracy and Illegal Gambling[]
Piracy is illegal film theft. This involves selling pirated copies of a movie/ Illegal gambling involves taking bets while residing in Nations that do not allow gambling. 

Twerking[]
These involve crashing a party and twerking on a stranger. Funnily enough, it can get you life in prison!

All Delinquent Actions[]
+ denotes disorderly conduct.
- denotes criminal mischief
= denotes reckless endangerment
@ denotes others.








Delinquency













Blowing up (fruit) using illegal fireworks. -
Blowing up your neighbor's mailbox using an M-80. -
Breaking into my neighbor's house while they weren't home to play their new video game system. @
Collecting all the coins from the local fountain.
Destroying mailboxes using a (Weapon) -
Dropping water balloons from an overpass onto cars that passed below. =
Dumping all of your trash into a neighbor's yard. -
Egging a local (place)
Flushing lit firecrackers down the toilet at a local (place) -
Getting onto the elevator of the tallest building in my city and pressed every single button. +
Going downtown and keying a magician's car. -
Going to a local high school volleyball game and yelled insults at the players from the sideline. +
Going to a nearby skyscraper and spit out the window from the top floor. +
Hiding inside the clothing racks at a clothing store and scaring shoppers as they walked by. +
Illegally taking bets on the (competition). @
Locking locked a (random stranger) into a bathroom at a local (place). =
Mowing a neighbor's flower garden, killing all of the flowers. -
Noticing that a neighbor left her keys in her new sports car, so taking it for a joyride. -
Pouring gallons of food coloring into a public fountain. -
Pouring laundry detergent into a public fountain. -
Pulling a fire alarm at the largest apartment complex in town at 3AM. +
Rearranging the mannequins at a clothing store into a variety of naughty sexual positions. -
Releasing three pigs, labelled "Pig #1", "Pig #2", and "Pig #4" into the local high school. +
Riding a (transport) through a local (attraction) wearing a (costume) costume while (doing weird action). +
Running onto the field and slid into second base at a professional baseball game. +
Selling a bag of fake marijuana to some college kids. @
Selling some pirated copies of "(film)" at a local farmers market. @
Setting a broom on fire and threw it off the roof of a building. =
Setting up an extremely loud stereo system outside of city hall and blasting a (Music) album. +
Slapping (stranger) for no reason while walking downtown @
Shooting out the windows of a decrepit, abandoned building. -
Slashing a stranger's tires in a busy parking lot. -
Stealing a street sign late at night when nobody was around. -
Stealing an unlocked bike I found at a nearby apartment complex. @
Stopping traffic during rush hour to do a lip-synced performance of a (band) song from the middle of a crosswalk. =
Stripping off my clothes and streaking across a college campus. +
Switching a bunch of price tags at a local electronics store. @
Tagging a local (place), writing "Your mom loves you!/Sorry about your wall!/Tag! You're it!/ You want some tuna?/I hate being bipolar! It's awesome!/ What are you looking at?" -
Throwing beer bottles onto oncoming traffic. =
Throwing (food) into the neighbor's yard. =
Throwing snowballs at people who were getting out of their cars in a local (place) parking lot. =
Toilet papering your neighbor's house using (number) rolls of TP. -
Twerking on a (random stranger) while hanging out downtown. @
Using a permanent marker to draw (Private parts) on street signs. -
Using a water balloon launcher to shoot water balloons at your neighbor's house =
Went to a sports bar during the (Sports Event) and used an universal remote control to turn off all of the televisions in a (Great Moment) moment. @
Writing "Hammer Time" underneath the word "Stop" on every stop sign in town. -







Consequences[]
Sometimes when you do these actions, there are many popups who can appear&#160;:

Argue: A parent with high religiousness will argue with your character.
Arrested: Sometimes you can be arrested for your crime, if you are minor, you will be send to Juvenile Center without a trial.
Being addicted to alcohol: Likely go on party with your friends/best friend, you can suffer from an addiction to alcohol.





